{
    "id": "7fd60e46e8d04eed9ffaa48f9d68da8b",
    "title": "Rewrite with nouns",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "a2c7620d1ea646df9fc1d332c61a24d1",
            "title": "Nouns Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "That kind of movies doesn’t give me any ........................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "amuse",
                        "amusement",
                        "amusing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The .................................. of this article is $",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "cost",
                        "costs"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He is a .................................. to his family.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "disgrace",
                        "disgraceful",
                        "disgraced"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He put up a brave .........................................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "fighting",
                        "fight"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He gave a curt .....................................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "reply",
                        "replied",
                        "replying"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "There is a slight .................................. between these two shades.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "difference",
                        "different",
                        "differ"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I see him ..................................",
                    "description": "Daily is an adverb.",
                    "answers": [
                        "daily",
                        "every day"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He read the letter with .....................................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "care",
                        "caring",
                        "careful"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Though the ant is small it has as much ..................................... as the elephant.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "intelligence",
                        "intelligent",
                        "intelligently"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He is so industrious that he wins everybody’s .......................................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "admiration",
                        "admire",
                        "admiringly"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}